

NZ Permanent Resident



Auckland, NZ



+64 20 4117 8536



bertoni_elisa@hotmail.com







PROJECTS

<u>Devfolio</u> - a website showcasing all my past and ongoing projects.

MyLibrary - my first solo fullstack project, including unit tests covering over 80% of functions in the repo.

Gallerina - final Dev Academy group project. An art curation website that allows users to create their own curations of some of the most famous art pieces in the world. I developed the layout and features of the homepage and contributed to the styling of the entire website using Tailwind. I was also in charge of all PR and merges.

MyVino - WIP wine cellar management app.



TECH STACK

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- HTML
- CSS
- React
- Express
- Knex
- Git

ELISA BERTONI

Full Stack Software Developer



ABOUT ME

I am a software developer with a background in customer service. My professional and personal interests have led me to enjoy a 10-year career in the hospitality industry in several countries around the world.

I have a keen eye for detail, strong organisational skills and impeccable customer service.

Working very closely with hospitality and stock management software made me realise how much I love tech but also how limited some of those software are. Hopefully I will get to develop my own one day!



EXPERIENCE

TRAINEE | DEV ACADEMY AOTEAROA

Remote, NZ

Jan 2023 - May 2023

An intensive 17-week web development training replicating real-life work environment by using agile methodologies.

The programme involved over 800 hours of hands-on coding where I learnt and became familiar with Git, HTML, CSS, JavaScript and TypeScript, React, Redux, Knex, TTD and unit testing, just to name a few.

The Bootcamp is packed with daily coding challenges, completed solo or in pairs, as well as weekly 24-hour group projects in teams of 4. The programme culminated with a five-day self-directed group project presented to a non-technical audience during graduation night.

Alongside tech concepts, there is also a huge emphasis on soft skills and we often discussed about empathy, self-compassion and wellbeing. I also had opportunity to practice Nonviolent Communication, active listening, and providing and receiving growth feedback.

EDUCATION

DEV ACADEMY AOTEAROA

Certificate in Applied Software Development

Jan 2023 - May 2023

EIT HAWKE'S BAY

Diploma in Information Systems 2021-2022

UNIVERSITY OF MARBURG

Exchange - Erasmus Programme Feb 2012 - July 2012

UNIVERSITY OF MILAN

Bachelor's in Tourism, Geography and Environmental

2009-2013



LANGUAGES

Native Italian

Intermediate German

INTERESTS & HOBBIES

Outside of work I like cooking, eating good food and drinking fine wine. I also love cycling, playing cards and jigsaw puzzles. I am an eager traveler and you can often find me at the beach.



ELISA BERTONI

Full Stack Software Developer



EXPERIENCE

CELLAR DOOR DUTY MANAGER | PR WINEMAKERS NZ

Napier, NZ

Sep 2020 - ongoing

Overseeing the day-to-day operations of Church Road Cellar Door and supporting the team while they deliver premium tasting experiences and winery tours to visitors.

In-house tech support for the Cellar Door team, including troubleshooting till and eftpos-related issues and support staff with the company's cloud system, e.g. when encountering syncing issues.

Extensive use of ResDiary, SwiftPOS and EposNow.

TRAVEL AGENT | ANTIPODEAN LUXURY TRAVEL

Havelock North, NZ

Feb 2020 - Jun 2020

Organising bespoke travel itineraries and events for high-end clientele visiting New Zealand from overseas.

Even if for a short amount of time, this job gave me the opportunity to hold courageous conversations. A month into this position COVID-19 blew up and I had to face difficult conversations with not-so-pleasant customers wanting refunds on their prepaid upcoming trips.

Extensive use of HubSpot and Wetu.

RESTAURANT MANAGER | BISTRONOMY

Napier, NZ

Sep 2017 - Feb 2020

Leading and managing a team of 10-15 floor staff in a fast-paced 2 hats restaurant enabled me to practice leadership, resilience and working under pressure.

Stock and cash management helped me develop strong organisation skills.

Extensive use of Menumate(now POSbiz) and Eveve NZ.

Previous Overseas Experience Available on Request